(Penny:)I'm fine.
(Amy:)Oh, who are you kidding?
She's breathtaking.
(Priya:)So, Penny,
(Priya:)Leonard tells me
you're an actress.
(Priya:)That must be
pretty exciting.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, yeah.
It's real great.
(Penny:)Today I drove to Van Nuys
for an audition
(Penny:)I thought was going to be
for a cat food commercial.
(Penny:)Turned out to be porn.
(Sheldon:)Did you get the part?
(Penny:)I didn't do the audition.
(Sheldon:)Given the state of your career,
(Sheldon:)can you really afford
to be picky?
(Priya:)I took acting classes
when I was at Cambridge.
(Priya:)I loved it.
We did Taming
of the Shrew.
(Leonard:)Oh, wow. I love
Taming of the Shrew.
(Leonard:)I did a paper
on it in high school.
"Who knows not where
a wasp does wear his sting?
In his tail."
"In his tongue""
"Whose tongue?"
"Yours, if you
talk of tails,
and so farewell."
"What, with my tongue
in your tail?"